Guide to the Warren Platner Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Warren Platner records
1960-2005
MS 1874
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
326.5
(164 boxes)
The records contain drawings, photographs, correspondence, job files, and publicity records documenting the career of Warren Platner as an architect and designer. The records include extensive documentation of major projects, such as Standard Brands, Kent Memorial Library, Sea Containers, Windows on the World at the World Trade Center, and Water Tower Place. The records document Platner's career as an associate at the offices of both Eero Saarinen and Kevin Roche John Dinkeloo, as well as his independent work. The collection contains only minimal documentation of Platner's furniture designs for Knoll.
Platner, Warren, 1919-2006
Biographical / Historical
Joseph Warren Platner was born on June 18, 1919, in Baltimore, Maryland. After graduating from Cornell in 1941, he worked in the architecture offices of both I. M. Pei and Eero Saarinen. After Saarinen's death, Platner continued to work as head of interior design for Kevin Roche John Dinkeloo and Associates, collaborating most significantly on the Ford Foundation headquarters building in New York. In 1955, he was awarded the Rome Prize for architecture. Platner opened his own firm, Platner Associates, in New Haven in the late 1960s, and is known best for his line of furniture designed for Knoll, his interiors for Water Tower Place in Chicago and Windows on the World in New York, and renovations of the Yale Club and the Pan Am/MetLife Building, also in New York. He was inducted into the Interior Design Magazine Hall of Fame in 1985. Platner died on April 20, 2006, in New Haven, Connecticut.
Scope and Contents
The records contain drawings, photographs, correspondence, job files, and publicity records documenting the career of Warren Platner as an architect and designer. The records include extensive documentation of major projects, such as Standard Brands, Kent Memorial Library, Sea Containers, Windows on the World at the World Trade Center, and Water Tower Place. The records document Platner's career as an associate at the offices of both Eero Saarinen and Kevin Roche John Dinkeloo, as well as his independent work. The collection contains only minimal documentation of Platner's furniture designs for Knoll.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Bronson Platner, 2006.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Arrangement
The records are arranged alphabetically by project.
Other Finding Aids
For a list of projects and the boxes in which project materials are located, please consult the Project Index.
Furniture design; Platner, Warren, 1919-2006; Saarinen, Eero, 1910-1961; Kent Memorial Library (Suffield, Conn.); Knoll International, Inc; Windows on the World (New York, N.Y.)
- Project Records
  Other Finding Aids
  For a list of projects and the boxes in which project materials are located, please consult the Project Index.
  - 21 Club: Upstairs at 21, 1997
    Scope and Contents
    Job location: New York, NY
    Photographer: Peter Mauss/ESTO, Wayne Evans
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
    - Drawings (Box 1, Box 81)
    - Photographs (Box 1)
    - Slides (Box 1)
  - 625 Madison Avenue Artwork
    - Drawings (Box 1, Box 149)
    - Slides (Box 1)
    - Negatives (Box 1)
    - Transparencies (Box 1)
  - 900 North Michigan, 1992
    Photographer: Wolfgang Hoyt/ESTO
    - Photographs (Box 1)
    - Slides (Box 1)
    - Negatives (Box 1)
  - American Embassy London
    Job location: London, England
    - Photographs (Box 1)
    - Slides (Box 1)
  - American Restaurant (Crown Center), 1974
    Job location: Kansas City, MO Collaborator: Edward Larrabee Barnes (architect) Photographer: Alexandre Georges
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
    - Drawings (Box 1)
    - Photographs (Box 1)
    - Slides (Box 1)
    - Negatives (Box 1)
    - Transparencies (Box 1)
  - American Standard, 1979-1989
    Job location: Toronto
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1, Box 8)
    - Photographs (Box 1)
    - Slides (Box 1)
    - Negatives (Box 1)
    - Transparencies (Box 1)
    - Electronic Records and Videos (Box 2–7)
  - Apex L.L. Evan, 1981
    Photographer: Peter Aaron/ESTO
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8)
    - Drawings (Box 8)
    - Photographs (Box 8)
    - Slides (Box 8)
    - Transparencies (Box 8)
  - Bell Laboratories, 1962-1964
    Job location: Holmdel, NJ
    Collaborator: Eero Saarinen (architect)
    Photographer: Joseph W. Molitor
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8)
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Berlin, Capital District of
    Job location: Berlin, Germany
    - Slides (Box 8)
    - Transparencies (Box 8)
  - Bertoia, Harry - bronze
    - Slides (Box 8)
  - Brandeis University: Chapel, 1951-1953
    Job location: Massachusetts
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8)
    - Negatives (Box 8)
  - Buffalo Museum
    Job location: Buffalo, NY
    - Drawings (Box 8, Box 81)
    - Slides (Box 8)
    - Negatives (Box 8)
  - Calligraphy Chair Samples
    - Transparencies (Box 8)
  - Chapel Square Office Building, 1987-1989
    Job location: New Haven, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8)
    - Drawings (Box 8)
  - Columbia Broadcast System (CBS) [general], 1978
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8)
  - Columbia Broadcast System (CBS) Airplane, 1969
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Columbia Broadcast System (CBS) Building, 1978-1980
    Photographer: Ezra Stoller
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8)
    - Drawings (Box 8)
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Columbia Broadcast System (CBS) Ground Floor, 1975
    Photographer: Alexandre Georges
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 9)
    - Drawings (Box 9)
    - Photographs (Box 9)
    - Slides (Box 9)
    - Transparencies (Box 9)
  - Columbia Broadcast System (CBS) Restaurant
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 9)
  - Columbia Broadcast System (CBS) Specialty Stores (Pacific Stereo), 1978-1980
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 9)
    - Drawings (Box 82)
    - Photographs (Box 9)
  - C.I. Designs, 1969-1970
    Job location: Boston, MA
    Photographer: Ezra Stoller, Phokion Karas
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 9)
    - Drawings (Box 83–85)
    - Photographs (Box 9, Box 25)
    - Slides (Box 9)
    - Negatives (Box 9)
    - Transparencies (Box 9)
  - Concordia College
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 9)
  - Cooper Residence, 1954
    Photographer: Richard Shirk
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 9)
    - Photographs (Box 9)
    - Transparencies (Box 9)
  - Crown Center, 1973-1985
    Job location: Kansas City, MO
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 9)
  - Corry-Jamestown Source Group
    Job location: Corry, PA
    Photographer: Sherwin Greenberg, McGranahan & May, Inc.; Ezra Stoller
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 9)
    - Photographs (Box 9)
    - Negatives (Box 9)
  - Dagworthy, Judith, 1986-1990
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
  - Dave's Model (Dark/Light)
    - Slides (Box 10)
  - John Deere and Company, 1961-1964
    Job location: Moline, IL
    Collaborator: Eero Saarinen, Kevin Roche (architects)
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
    - Drawings (Box 10, Box 164)
    - Photographs (Box 10)
    - Slides (Box 10)
    - Negatives (Box 10)
    - Transparencies (Box 10)
  - Detroit Federal Reserve Bank
    Job location: Detroit, MI
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
  - Dover Ferryships (Sealink), 1990
    Job location: Dover, England
    Photographer: Kenneth Champlin, Paul Robinson
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
    - Photographs (Box 10)
    - Slides (Box 10)
    - Transparencies (Box 10)
  - Dow Executive Center, 1981
    - Photographs (Box 10)
    - Slides (Box 10)
  - Dulles International Airport
    Job location: Washington, D.C.
    Photographer: Baltazar Korab, Joseph Molitor
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 10)
    - Drawings (Box 10)
    - Photographs (Box 10)
    - Slides (Box 10)
  - Eames, Charles and Ray - House
    Job location: Los Angeles, CA
    - Slides (Box 10)
  - Elevator
    - Drawings (Box 81)
  - Fermi, Enrico - Memorial
    - Negatives (Box 10)
  - Fain Residence, 1990
    Photographer: Aaron Usher
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 11)
    - Photographs (Box 11)
    - Slides (Box 11)
    - Transparencies (Box 11)
  - Faulkner, Dawkins, and Sullivan
    Job location: NYC, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 11)
    - Drawings (Box 11)
    - Photographs (Box 11)
    - Slides (Box 11)
    - Transparencies (Box 11)
  - Fayerweather Gymnasium, Wesleyan University, 1978
    Job location: Middletown, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 11)
  - Fields, Edward
    - Transparencies (Box 11)
  - Ford Foundation, 1968
    Collaborator: Kevin Roche (architect)
    Photographer: Norman McGrath, Ezra Stoller
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 11)
    - Photographs (Box 11)
    - Slides (Box 11)
    - Transparencies (Box 11)
  - Friedman Residence
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 11)
    - Slides (Box 11)
    - Negatives (Box 11)
  - Furniture, Wire -- Miscellaneous
    - Drawings (Box 85–87)
  - Gelco, 1974-1975
    - Photographs (Box 11)
    - Slides (Box 11)
    - Negatives (Box 11)
  - General Motors Technical Center
    Job location: Michigan
    Photographer: Lionel Freedman, Richard Shirk, Ezra Stoller
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 11)
    - Drawings (Box 11)
    - Photographs (Box 11)
    - Slides (Box 11)
    - Negatives (Box 11)
  - Georg Jensen Showroom, 1968
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 11)
    - Drawings (Box 11)
    - Photographs (Box 11)
    - Slides (Box 11)
    - Negatives (Box 11)
  - Guilford [Platner] Loft
    Job location: Guilford, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 11)
    - Drawings (Box 11)
    - Slides (Box 11)
    - Negatives (Box 11)
    - Transparencies (Box 11)
  - Guilford [Platner] Loft (Garage Apartment)
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 11)
    - Photographs (Box 11)
  - Guilford [Platner] Residence, 1971
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 11–12)
    - Drawings (Box 11–12)
    - Photographs (Box 11–12)
    - Slides (Box 11–12)
    - Negatives (Box 11–12)
    - Transparencies (Box 11–12)
  - Harvard/Kresge
    - Drawings (Box 12)
    - Slides (Box 12)
  - "Heart of Atlanta" and "Underground Atlanta"
    Job location: Atlanta, GA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 12)
  - Hicks, Sheila/Platner, Warren exhibit, 1968
    Job location: Paris, France
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 12)
  - Hicks, Sheila: Tapestries, 1968
    Collaborator: Sheila Hicks
    Photographer: Ferdinand Boesch
    - Photographs (Box 12)
  - Hicks, Sheila: Zanartu, 1971-1972
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 12)
  - Historic Landmarks, 1978-1979
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 13)
  - Howenstein Residence, 1982
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 13)
    - Drawings (Box 13)
    - Photographs (Box 13)
    - Slides (Box 13)
    - Negatives (Box 13)
    - Transparencies (Box 13)
  - IBM [general]
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 13)
  - IBM Dining Room
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 13)
  - IBM Yorktown
    - Slides (Box 13)
  - Jefferson National Expansion Memorial
    Job location: St. Louis, MO
    - Photographs (Box 13)
  - Johnson, Philip Residence
    - Slides (Box 25)
  - Jordan (Government Hospitality Center)
    Job location: Amman, Jordan
    - Drawings (Box 13)
    - Slides (Box 13)
    - Negatives (Box 13)
  - Kent Memorial Library, 1972
    Job location: Suffield, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 14–15)
    - Drawings (Box 13)
    - Photographs (Box 13)
    - Slides (Box 13)
    - Negatives (Box 13)
    - Transparencies (Box 13)
  - Knoll Factory Tour
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Knoll Furniture, 1967-1971
    Photographer: Joe A. Watson, Robert Perron
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 16)
    - Drawings (Box 88–90)
    - Photographs (Box 16)
    - Slides (Box 16)
  - Knoll Modular Desk and Wall System
    Photographer: Gene B. Hasbrouck, Norman McGrath
    - Photographs (Box 16)
  - Knoll Office: Desks and Cabinets, with legs
    - Transparencies (Box 16)
  - Knoll Furniture: Wire Collection
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 16)
    - Photographs (Box 16, Box 25)
  - Larson, Jack Lenore
    - Drawings (Box 91)
  - Lehigh Furniture, 1968
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 16)
    - Drawings (Box 92–94)
    - Photographs (Box 16)
    - Slides (Box 16)
  - Lighthouse Point Park, 1992
    - Drawings (Box 25)
    - Photographs (Box 17)
    - Slides (Box 17)
    - Negatives (Box 17)
  - Lincoln Center Theater [Vivian Beaumont]
    Collaborator: Eero Saarinen, Jo Mielziner
    - Drawings (Box 17)
  - Lipchitz, Jacques
    - Photographs (Box 17)
    - Negatives (Box 17)
  - Lobster Lounge
    - Photographs (Box 17)
    - Slides (Box 17)
    - Transparencies (Box 17)
  - Lodge at Vail, 1983-1984
    Job location: Vail, CO
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 17–19)
    - Drawings (Box 95–109)
    - Photographs (Box 19)
    - Transparencies (Box 19)
  - Lodge at Vail: Artwork
    - Photographs (Box 19)
    - Transparencies (Box 19)
  - Lodge at Vail: Guest Rooms
    - Drawings (Box 19, Box 110)
    - Photographs (Box 19)
    - Slides (Box 19)
    - Negatives (Box 19)
    - Transparencies (Box 19)
  - Lodge at Vail: Model
    - Photographs (Box 19)
    - Slides (Box 19)
    - Transparencies (Box 19)
  - Lodge at Vail: Wildflower Restaurant
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 18–19)
    - Drawings (Box 111)
    - Photographs (Box 19)
    - Slides (Box 19)
  - Lusher Apartment at the Carlyle Hotel, 1988-1991
    Job location: New York, New York
    Photographer: Tina Freeman
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 19)
    - Photographs (Box 19)
    - Negatives (Box 19)
    - Transparencies (Box 19)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: Chapel and Kresge Auditorium
    Job location: Cambridge, MA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 20)
    - Slides (Box 20)
  - McCullough Residence
    - Photographs (Box 20)
    - Slides (Box 20)
  - Michigan State Capitol
    Job location: East Lansing, MI
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 20)
  - MGIC Investment Corporation Headquarters, 1973
    Job location: Milwaukee, WI
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 20–27)
    - Drawings (Box 21–25, Box 27, Box 42, Box 112–114)
    - Photographs (Box 21)
    - Slides (Box 21)
    - Negatives (Box 21)
    - Transparencies (Box 21)
  - MGIC Sculpture ("Le Grand Double")
    Job location: Milwaukee, WI Collaborator: Alicia Penalba Photographer: Martine Franck
    - Photographs (Box 25, Box 27)
    - Slides (Box 27)
  - Montreal
    - Slides (Box 27)
  - New School for Social Research
    - Photographs (Box 25)
    - Negatives (Box 25)
  - New York Apartment
    Job location: New York
    - Drawings (Box 27)
  - Newark Hotel, Airport
    Job location: Newark, NJ
    Photographer: Charles Schulze, Gil Amiaga
    - Photographs (Box 27)
    - Slides (Box 27)
  - Norman Rockwell Museum
    Job location: Stockbridge, MA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 28)
    - Drawings (Box 28)
    - Photographs (Box 28)
    - Slides (Box 28)
    - Negatives (Box 28)
  - Nova Presentation
    - Drawings (Box 28)
  - OCBC Singapore
    - Photographs (Box 28)
  - Office Floor Plan, Typical
    - Drawings (Box 81)
  - Office Photographs, 1986
    - Photographs (Box 28)
  - Orient Express
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 28)
  - Paintings
    - Slides (Box 28)
  - Pan Am: Renovations, 1986-1987
    Photographer: Peter Mauss/ESTO; Bernstein Assoc., Inc.
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 28)
    - Drawings (Box 22, Box 115–123)
    - Photographs (Box 28)
    - Slides (Box 28)
    - Negatives (Box 28)
    - Transparencies (Box 28)
  - Paris Exhibition, Centre Culturel Americain
    - Photographs (Box 29)
  - Piano
    - Drawings (Box 85)
    - Slides (Box 29)
  - Pier 88
    - Photographs (Box 29)
    - Slides (Box 29)
    - Negatives (Box 29)
  - Platner, Warren -- Publicity and other professional and personal materials
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 30–31, Box 80)
    - Photographs (Box 30)
    - Slides (Box 31)
  - Porter, Wright, Morris and Arthur [PWMA]
    Job location: Columbus, OH
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 35)
    - Drawings (Box 29, Box 32–35, Box 124–126)
    - Photographs (Box 29, Box 32–33)
    - Slides (Box 29, Box 32–33)
    - Negatives (Box 29, Box 31–33)
    - Transparencies (Box 29, Box 32–33)
  - Princeton Prospect Center, 1970
    Job location: Princeton, NJ
    Photographer: Ezra Stoller, Norman McGrath
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 34)
    - Drawings (Box 34)
    - Photographs (Box 34)
    - Slides (Box 34)
    - Negatives (Box 34)
    - Transparencies (Box 34)
  - Providence Atheneum, 1978-1979
    Job location: Providence, RI
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 34, Box 36–38, Box 42)
    - Drawings (Box 34, Box 36–38, Box 42, Box 127)
    - Photographs (Box 34)
    - Slides (Box 34)
    - Negatives (Box 34)
    - Transparencies (Box 34)
  - Providence Journal, 1974-1978
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 39)
    - Photographs (Box 39)
    - Slides (Box 39)
    - Negatives (Box 39)
    - Transparencies (Box 39)
  - Raffles City, 1981
    Job location: Singapore
    - Photographs (Box 39)
  - Recondo Triptych
    - Slides (Box 39)
  - Riverdale Country School, 1974-1980
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 39)
    - Drawings (Box 39)
    - Photographs (Box 39)
    - Slides (Box 39)
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Rockefeller Center: Promenade Cafes, 1969
    - Drawings (Box 39)
    - Photographs (Box 39)
    - Negatives (Box 39)
  - Rouse Atlanta (Model), 1986
    - Photographs (Box 39)
    - Slides (Box 39)
    - Transparencies (Box 39)
  - Rouse (New Haven)
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 39)
  - School, "Linda's Drawings", 1976
    - Slides (Box 39)
  - Schulten Residence
    - Drawings (Box 25)
    - Negatives (Box 25)
  - Sculpture (Fountain Sculpture and Others)
    - Photographs (Box 39)
  - Sculptures in wood
    Photographer: Hedrich-Blessing
    - Photographs (Box 39)
    - Slides (Box 39)
  - Sea Containers [King's Reach section of the Thames River], 1981-1987; 1985-1994
    Photographer: Wolfgang Hoyt/ESTO, Dorothy Alexander, Peter Schuerd, Sir Robert McAlpine & Sons, Ltd.
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 25, Box 39–49)
    - Drawings (Box 25, Box 39–48, Box 128–144)
    - Photographs (Box 25, Box 39–40)
    - Slides (Box 39)
    - Negatives (Box 39)
    - Transparencies (Box 25, Box 39)
  - Seattle Theater
    - Negatives (Box 49)
  - Seligson
    - Photographs (Box 49)
    - Transparencies (Box 49)
  - Ship Models (Flomex, Princess Marguerite)
    - Photographs (Box 49)
  - Ships (Princess Marguerite, Contender/Flomex)
    Photographer: Kenneth Champlin
    - Photographs (Box 49)
  - Shopping Mall
    - Drawings (Box 81)
  - Sinai Temple
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 50)
    - Drawings (Box 50)
    - Photographs (Box 50)
    - Slides (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Transparencies (Box 50)
  - Singapore: Compass Rose and Chinese Overseas Bank
    - Slides (Box 50)
    - Transparencies (Box 50)
  - Southwest Washington Redevelopment
    Photographer: Lionel Freedman
    - Photographs (Box 50)
  - Standard Brands Research Center, 1978-1979
    Job location: Wilton, CT
    Photographer: Dave Rentz, Ezra Stoller
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 51–53, Box 55–68)
    - Drawings (Box 25, Box 50, Box 53–56, Box 59–68, Box 145–147)
    - Photographs (Box 25, Box 50–51)
    - Slides (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Transparencies (Box 50)
  - Steelcase [general]
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 67)
  - Steelcase Multiple Shell Seating and Tables (6403)
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 67)
    - Photographs (Box 67)
    - Slides (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Transparencies (Box 67)
  - Steelcase Furniture
    - Drawings (Box 148)
    - Photographs (Box 25)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Transparencies (Box 67)
  - Steelcase Furniture (Shell and Frame Seating, Multiple Shell 6402), 1967
    Photographer: Alexandre Georges, Robert Perron, Gene B. Hasbrouck, Ezra Stoller
    - Photographs (Box 25, Box 67)
    - Slides (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Transparencies (Box 67)
  - Steelcase Office (9 West)
    - Negatives (Box 69)
  - Steelcase Showroom, 1969
    Job location: Chicago, IL
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 69)
    - Drawings (Box 69, Box 149)
    - Photographs (Box 69)
    - Negatives (Box 69)
  - Table [unidentified]
    - Drawings (Box 85)
  - Tanglewood Music Shed - Boston Symphony Orchestra, 1970-1971
    Job location: Lenox, MA
    Collaborator: Saarinen, Swanson and Saarinen (architects)
    Photographer: Norman McGrath
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 69–70)
    - Drawings (Box 69–70, Box 150)
    - Photographs (Box 69)
    - Slides (Box 69)
    - Negatives (Box 69)
  - Taylor Residence
    Photographer: Richard Shirk, Ezra Stoller
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 70)
    - Photographs (Box 70)
    - Slides (Box 70)
    - Negatives (Box 70)
  - Teknor-Apex Company Headquarters, 1974
    Job location: Pawtucket, RI
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 71)
    - Drawings (Box 71)
    - Photographs (Box 71)
    - Slides (Box 71)
    - Negatives (Box 71)
    - Transparencies (Box 71)
  - Ten by Warren Platner [book], 1975
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 71)
    - Slides (Box 71)
    - Negatives (Box 71)
    - Transparencies (Box 71)
  - Texas Com. Tower
    Job location: Houston, TX
    - Negatives (Box 71)
  - TWA [general], 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 71)
  - TWA "Le Monde" Restaurant and TWA Terminal, 1960
    Photographer: Alexandre Georges, Ezra Stoller
    - Drawings (Box 71)
    - Photographs (Box 71)
    - Slides (Box 71)
    - Negatives (Box 71)
  - TWA Ambassador's Club, 1960
    - Photographs (Box 71)
    - Slides (Box 71)
  - University of Chicago Law School
    - Photographs (Box 71)
  - University of Pennsylvania: Women's Residence
    Job location: Philadelphia, PA
    Photographer: Lawrence Williams, Baltazar Korab
    - Photographs (Box 71)
    - Slides (Box 71)
  - Vassar/Victoria Station
    - Slides (Box 71)
  - Wagner Residence
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 71)
    - Photographs (Box 71)
    - Slides (Box 71)
  - Wall Street Square, 1986
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 71)
    - Drawings (Box 71)
    - Photographs (Box 71)
    - Slides (Box 71)
    - Negatives (Box 71)
    - Transparencies (Box 71)
  - Water Tower Place, 1972-1976
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 25, Box 72–73)
    - Drawings (Box 25, Box 151–156)
    - Photographs (Box 25, Box 72)
    - Slides (Box 72)
    - Negatives (Box 72)
    - Transparencies (Box 71–72)
  - Wesleyan University, Fayerweather Hall, 1977-1981
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 73)
    - Drawings (Box 73)
    - Photographs (Box 73)
    - Slides (Box 73)
    - Negatives (Box 73)
    - Transparencies (Box 73)
  - Whitney-Grove
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 73)
  - Windemere Island Club
    Job location: Greenwich, CT
    - Negatives (Box 73)
  - World Trade Center -- Windows on the World Restaurant, and Observation Deck., 1976
    Photographer: Alexandre Georges, Ezra Stoller, Jaime Ardiles-Arce, Ross Elmi
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 79)
    - Drawings (Box 73, Box 76–77, Box 79, Box 157–163)
    - Photographs (Box 25, Box 74)
    - Slides (Box 72–73)
    - Negatives (Box 75)
    - Transparencies (Box 74–75)
  - Wright Residence
    - Slides (Box 78)
  - Yale Club: lobby (renovations), 1971
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 80)
    - Drawings (Box 80, Box 164)
    - Photographs (Box 80)
    - Slides (Box 80)
    - Transparencies (Box 80)
  - Yale University: Morse and Stiles Colleges
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 80)
    - Drawings (Box 80)
    - Photographs (Box 80)
    - Slides (Box 80)
  - Yale University: Mathematics Building Competition, 1969